
To Do

Ideas
- Script to merge partitions
- Allow time window for Data to be switched to MeasurementStore, not just low water mark
- Fast count for empty all data

Done
- Allow time window for Data to be switched to MeasurementStore, not just low water mark
- Print rausnehmen
- Keep tables if they are switched out
- Nur Remove Tage wenn daten drin sind 
- Create a transfer schema 
- Try catch
